JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 21
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 1
SAVORY BREAD / GARLIC BREAD /
APPLE PIE / SLICED BREAD / MILK BREAD / RUSKS /
CROISSANTS / DONUTS /
PIZZA BREAD / CORNBREAD
CHOCOLATE MUFFINS
SLICED BREAD / CROISSANTS
KATSU SANDWICH
LENT
BUDOGAOKA MIDDLE SCHOOL
MORIOH LANDMARK #7
"BAKERY ST. GENTLEMEN"
HOW TO GET THERE: TAKE THE "MORIOH
BUDOGAOKA HIGH SCHOOL" BUS
TO ITS FINAL STOP AND
WALK TWO MINUTES ON
THE GREEN ROAD FROM THE STATION.
STUDENTS, HOUSEWIVES,
AND OFFICE LADIES RAVE ABOUT
ITS VARIETY OF STONE-OVEN BAKED BREADS.
DON'T MISS THEIR BEST SELLER:
SANDWICHES. BEWARE, THEY SELL OUT FAST.
EPISODE 22
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 2